

Trang Nguyen

Commercial Director, Head of Physical Categories at Sendo.vn

Connect

Message

More...



Try Premium Free for 1 Month





Connect Message

• • •

Trang Nguyen · 3rd

Commercial Director, Head of Physical Categories at Sendo.vn

Vietnam · 500+ connections · Contact info

Sendo^{*}

Sendo.vn

Institute for International Relations

People and pages related to Trang

See all



>







Page • Internet 267,158 followers

Follow

Follow



Flipkart
Page • Internet
2,022,645 followers

Follow

About

Experienced in e-commerce, online travel and ride hailing with strong focus on growth, efficiency and people. Successful leadership role in operation, sales and business development with P&L responsibility. Experienced in working with senior executives. Skillful in building team and motivating staffs. Worked in Japan, Philippines

... see more

Activity 3,045 followers



Beautiful!

Trang commented

See all activity

Experience

Sendo.vn

l yr 3 mos

Sendo Commercial Director, Head of Physical Categories

Full-time

Jan 2021 – Present

· 4 mos

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Head of Digital Goods & Services

Full-time

Feb 2020 – Jan 2021

· 1 yr

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Head of 4 Wheels



Agoda

10 yrs

ogoda Country Director, Vietnam

Feb 2011 - Sep 2018

· 7 yrs 8 mos

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Built and grew multi million dollar OTA business in Vietnam.

Senior Advisor - Hotels, Japan

Sep 2012 – May 2013

· 9 mos

Show 2 more roles ~

Vietnam Airlines

i yrs 10 mos



Dec 2007 – Sep 2008

· 10 mos

Director's Assistant

Dec 2001 – Dec 2007 · 6 yrs 1 mo Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Education

Institute for International Relations

BA, International Economics 1997 – 2001

Skills & endorsements

Online Travel . 55



Endorsed by Le Ngoc Thai Duong and 1 other who is highly skilled at this

agoda

Endorsed by 8 of Trang's colleagues at Agoda

Revenue Analysis . 39



Endorsed by Rajat Chhabra, CHA, who is highly skilled at this

agoda

Endorsed by 6 of Trang's colleagues at Agoda

Hotels . 36

agoda

Endorsed by 3 of Trang's colleagues at Agoda



Endorsed by 6 people who know Hotels

Industry Knowledge

Yield Management . 33

```
Tourism . 30
Hotel Management . 22
E-commerce . 21
Marketing Strategy . 20
Hotel Booking . 20
Online Marketing . 13
Business Strategy . 9
Sales Management . 9
Business Development . 7
Market Research . 6
Sales . 6
Marketing Management . 5
Hospitality Management . 5
Marketing . 4
Food & Beverage . 3
Event Management . 2
Online Advertising . 2
Leisure . 2
Business Planning . 1
Project Planning . 1
Operations Management . 1
```

```
Project Management . 1
Digital Marketing . 1
Pre-opening . 1
Front Office
Public Relations . 1
Interpersonal Skills
Management . 29
Negotiation . 15
Customer Service . 4
Contract Negotiation . 1
Other Skills 🔞
Hospitality . 30
Hospitality Industry . 10
Resorts . 4
Marketing Communications . 1
                                                                   Show less ^
Recommendations
```

Received (1) Given (4)



Trang has outstanding organizational skills. He is able to successfully complete multiple tasks with highest quality in our team. :)

Accomplishments

4

Languages

English • Vietnamese

Interests

McKinsey & Company



3,884,058 followers

Matt Higgins in



CEO and Co-Founder at RSE Ventures, Executive Fellow at Harvard Business Schoo

99,823 followers

Google



21,134,781 followers

Hot Jobs - Top Careers with L&A

Le & Associates 1,191 members

Amazon



19,052,249 followers

Navigos Search

3,238 members

See all

People also viewed



Vinh Lam •3rd

Marketplace Operation Director at Sendo.vn

Connect



Kevin Hoang •3rd

Market Manager at Agoda

Connect



Duc Pham •3rd

Business - Marketing - Operation | Buyer Engagement Director at Sendo.vn

Connect



Linh Trần Hải •3rd 📊

Sendo CEO

Connect



Thuy Dung Pham •3rd in

Market Manager at Agoda

Connect

∨Show more

People you may know



BE BA (My Nguyen)

Recruitment Specialist cum Admin at Milensea Retail

Connect



Le Nhat Huy

President at UTE Logistics and Supply Chain Club

Connect



Khánh Linh Đỗ

Human Resources Assistant at Hachinet Software

Connect



Nguyen Dinh Dat

Frontend Angular Developer

Connect



Nhi Duong

Stud	ent at	Ton	Duc	Thang	Un	iversity

Connect

∨Show more

Duc, learn what hiring managers look for in answers to top interview questions



Tell me about a time you had to persuade someone.



Tell me about a time you had to manage conflicting priorities.



Tell me about something you've accomplished that you are proud of.

See all questions

Linked in

About

Accessibility

alent Solutions	
Community Guidelines	
areers	
Marketing Solutions	
Privacy & Terms 💙	
d Choices	
dvertising	
ales Solutions	
Mobile Mobile	
mall Business	
afety Center	
Questions? (isit our Help Center.	
Manage your account and privacy to to your Settings.	
elect Language	
(Arabic) العربية	
inkedIn Corporation © 2021	
	ď

